[{"answer": "I'm going to have to say he lucky I'm a Christian.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 2, "question": "What is your view of him?", "qSentId": 1}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "OOPER, HOST, CNN'S AC360: Because of the only -- the two options you had, second-degree murder or manslaughter, you felt neither applied?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Did he ever talk to you about guns?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Did you ever see him with a gun?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "I'll hold it back.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What did that make you feel to see him again?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I'm not sure how she would have presented herself but certainly last night she was more engaging, more straightforward, more amiable, and I'm not sure why she started out with the attitude that she obviously did in the trial but certainly some of what she could have said was lost on the jury through the attitude.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Would she had been more engaging to the jury and would she have told us more about the other side of Trayvon martin that I don't think we really heard in that case?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "If he did throw the first blow against George Zimmerman because he was scared, why should that be the criteria that George Zimmerman escaping any kind of punishment when he shoots him dead?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "'MARA: Couple of answers.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Is that an area where the law could possibly be reviewed and possibly changed?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "No question.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Should he not when he was told we don't need you to do that, just turn around and go back in his car, and if he had done that or had he stayed in his car originally completely, do you accept that that would not have led to the catalyst of events that led to the shooting?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "There was no doubt in your mind from what Trayvon was telling you on the phone about the creepy ass cracker and so on that he absolutely believed that George Zimmerman, this man you didn't know who he was at the time, this man was pursuing him?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "And he was freaked out by it?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Couple of reasonable reactions.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Why should he lose his life because some guy is following him, and he's freaked out by it?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "That was our problem.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Did you feel like you understood the instructions from the judge because they were very complex?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Traditional self-defense, no.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Are there changes to the self-defense law you think that we should now consider as a result of all this?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "He'll never be able to just walk down the street and not worried who's going to hate him next.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "And do you think he'll ever be able to lead a normal life given all the mayhem that's erupted around this trial?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Really, what we were going to be in life.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What would you talk about?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "He was a good friend to you?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "A kind friend?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, it all started of course at the trial.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Tom, what was it about that interview and Rachel that made you think she deserves my help here?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "And then last night when I saw her on your show, you did a follow-up question that said what do you want to do in life?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Angry.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What do you feel about what that juror said about you?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, I think that as to Rachel Jeantel, obviously, she need to be prepared as a witness, and she didn't get the kind of preparation that she needed.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What are the lessons that we can learn from this trial, if any, going forward?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Oh yes, definitely I do empathize with them for sure.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Do you empathize with what they've had to endure?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "You think he racially profiled Trayvon Martin?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Oh, most definitely.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Do you stand by that decision that you took?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well, sorry, Lon, but I got to disagree with you on that uh -- I would have found him innocent on what they had -- what they had -- what the prosecution had given and it just seemed like everything was pretty shaky.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "And what would you have done with George Zimmerman based on the evidence that you have heard from that trial?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I mean in your jury deliberations, yeah.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "You mean like in jury deliberation?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Probably ten people.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "How many of your jury with OJ started off believing that he was guilty and changed their minds?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Ten and a half months.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Just how long were you sequestered?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think something was wrong with um -- I know they had asked the judge for some type of -- they had a question.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Could it be that they just ran out of energy and said let's just deal with this now?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I'm taken aback about your suit.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "I'm good, man, how you be?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Nick Cannon.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "The problem is the tie and the handkerchief because they are I believe which brand?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Uh, honestly I was disappointed in the verdict.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What do you think about the verdict?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I-I-I do, I do.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Do you think that Zimmerman racially profiled Trayvon Martin?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Yes, it's on right now.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) going well?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "You are missed.", "docId": "130716pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Surely not -- not with the great Howard Stern?", "qSentId": 539}]